RG 005:033, Office of the Governor: Abraham Ribicoff (1955-1961)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 7. Speeches
  - Kennedy, Sen[ator] John F., Nomination of for Vice Presidency [Democratic National Convention, Chicago] [Ribicoff’s revised copy], 1956 August 17 (Box 694)
  - Loeb Awards Presentation to Financial & Business Writers, New York, 1958 June 10 (Box 694)
  - Machine Tool Conference of the American Institute of Electrical Engineers [Statler-Hilton Hotel, Hartford, 1958 October 14 (Box 695)
  - “Management in Government,” Industrial Management Club of Southeastern Conn[ecticut], New London, 1958 July 7 (Box 695)
  - Manchester Chamber of Commerce, 1958 April 22 (Box 695)
  - Manufacturers Assoc[iation] of Conn[ecticut], 144th Annual Meeting, Yale University, 1959 September 15 (Box 695)
  - Manufacturers Assoc[iation] of Conn[ecticut], Yale University, (No Prepared Speech) [Digest of Welcoming], 1960 September 13 (Box 695)
  - Manufacturers Associ[ation] of Conn[ecticut], Yale University, Atomic Energy, 1956 September 12 (Box 695)
  - Manufacturers Ass[ociatio]n – Speeches [New Haven], 1958 September 9 (Box 695)
  - Mass[achusetts] Committee of Catholics, Protestants & Jews, Boston, 1956 May 17 (Box 695)
  - Mass[achusetts] Democratic State Convention, Worcester, 1956 June 8 (Box 695)
  - Mental Deficiency, American Ass[ociatio]n on, Hotel Statler, [Hartford], 1957 May 22 (Box 695)
  - Mental Health Conference, Northeast State Governments, 1959 April 9 (Box 695)
  - Mental Health, Conn[ecticut] Ass[ociatio]n for – WNHC Telecast – “In Mental Health”, 1958 June 18 (Box 695)
  - Mental Health, Conn[ecticut] Association of, New Haven, 1958 April 29 (Box 695)
  - (Mental Health) Pastoral Counseling, Holy Monastery, West Hartford, Conn[ecticut], 1960 April 25 (Box 695)
  - Meriden Chamber of Commerce, (Waverly Inn), 1960 April 28 (Box 695)
  - Meriden Democratic Town Committee, “Mentally Retarded Children”, 1958 October 21 (Box 695)
  - Meriden Station, [Radio Talk] John Stremlau, 1960 August 30 (Box 695)
  - Middletown Rotary Club Luncheon, 1960 January 12 (Box 695)
  - Middletown, Conn[ecticut], [Taxes and Budget], 1958 October 31 (Box 695)
  - Milford, Conn[ecticut], [Importance of Natural Resources in Development] (New State Park, etc.), 1958 October 28 (Box 695)
  - Mitchell College, New London (The Community College), 1958 April 17 (Box 695)
  - Morris, Conn[ecticut] [Second Annual East Shore Democratic Dinner] Fifth Congressional District Small Town Democrats, 1957 June 18 (Box 695)
  - Motor Transport Assoc[iation] of Conn[ecticut], (Fleet Traffic Safety Luncheon) Hartford, Conn[ecticut], 1958 September 25 (Box 695)
  - Media Advisory Group of President’s Committee for Traffic Safety, Hotel St. Regis, [New York City], 1956 December 12 (Box 695)
  - Mystic Seaport Museum [Twenty–Eighth Annual Meeting, Marine Historical Association, “What Mystic Seaport Means to Connecticut”], 1957 July 19 (Box 695)
  - Naugatuck Chamber of Commerce “The Future of Naugatuck”, 1957 December 3 (Box 695)
  - Naugatuck Democratic Rally, [Naugatuck’s Spirit of Recovery from the Flood], 1958 October 23 (Box 695)
  - New Britain Democratic Rally, Friday, 1958 October 31 (Box 695)
  - New Britain Hospital Nurses Alumnae Assoc[iation], 50th Anniv[ersary] Banquet, 1958 September 3 (Box 695)
  - New England Council, Hartford, (Salute to Insurance Industry), 1959 March 18 (Box 695)
  - New England Health Institute, Opening Session, University of Conn[ecticut], Storrs, 1958 June 18 (Box 695)
  - New Haven Taxpayers Research Council, “Economy in Government”, 1958 April 28 (Box 695)
  - New England Newspaper Advertising Executives Assoc[iation], [Summer Convention], Groton, Conn[ecticut], 1960 June 13 (Box 695)
  - Jewish Tercentenary [in the United States, Stamford, Spring, 1955 (Box 695)
  - Newtown Chamber of Commerce, 1958 February 11 (Box 695)
  - New York Mirror Youth Forum, 17th Annual, [Astor Hotel, New York City], 1959 December 5 (Box 695)
  - New York University – School of Education – Graduate Students Organization, 1956 December 13 (Box 695)
  - Northeast Resources Comm[ittee] Luncheon, Hotel Statler, H[art]f[or]d, 1958 April 15 (Box 695)
  - Norwich Tercentenary, Remarks by Governor Ribicoff at, 1959 July 6 (Box 695)
  - Norwich State Hospital – John Lodge Continued Treatment Building Dedication, 1956 December 28 (Box 695)
  - Ohlson, Agnes (Chief Nursing Examiner) [Testimonial Dinner], Statler Hotel, Hartford, 1957 October 16 (Box 695)
  - Pfizer, Charles, & Co[mpany], [Dedication of Medical Research Laboratories] Groton, Conn[ecticut], 1960 October 6 (Box 695)
  - P[arents] T[eachers] A[ssociation], Annual Convention, Berlin, Conn[ecticut], 1958 April 23 (Box 695)
  - P[arents] T[eachers] A[ssociation] – Gerrish – Overbrook PTA, East Haven, Conn[ecticut], 1958 October 7 (Box 695)
  - Pratt & Whitney 100th Anniversary Dinner [Hotel Bond, Hartford], 1960 May 18 (Box 695)
  - Presidential Election Campaign – Western Tour (Box 695)
  - Public Officials Traffic Safety Conference, Washington, D.C., 1957 December 9-10 (Box 695)
  - Radioisotopes Workshop, Connecticut Industrial, New Haven Lawn Club, 1960 March 30 (Box 695)
  - Read, D. M. Company, [Centennial Dinner] Bridgeport, Conn[ecticut], 1957 February 19 (Box 695)
  - Real Estate Boards, Conn[ecticut] Assoc[iation] of [Annual Convention] Hartford, Conn[ecticut], 1958 September 26 (Box 695)
  - Recreation, Governor’s Conference on, Hotel Statler [Hartford], 1960 September 12 (Box 695)
  - Red Cross, Conference for Volunteers, New Britain, C[onnecticu]t, 1958 October 24 (Box 695)
  - Red Cross Luncheon - New Haven, 1956 September 24 (Box 695)
  - Red Cross, Waldorf Astoria, N[ew] Y[ork] [City], 1956 February 20 (Box 695)
  - Northeast Regional Conference, National Association for Retarded Children, Hartford, 1958 June 8 (Box 695)
  - St. Joseph College Commencement Address, 1957 June 6 (Box 695)
  - St. Patrick’s Day Radio Program, [WBRY], 1960 March 13 (Box 695)
  - Sanders, W[illia]m J., Convocation of – Educ[ation] Comm[issioner], Bushnell, [Hartford], 1956 December 14 (Box 695)
  - Seymour Bridge Dedication (Gen[eral] Humphreys Memorial Bridge), 1958 August 19 (Box 695)
  - Silver Hill Foundation, [Dedication of] (Community Health Center), New Canaan, Conn[ecticut], 1958 September 27 (Box 695)
  - Stafford Springs “Pageant of Progress” Parade, 1960 September 17 (Box 695)
  - Stamford Democratic City Committee Dinner, Stamford, Conn[ecticut], 1958 August 23 (Box 695)
  - Stamford – Highway [Parking under viaducts of new Connecticut Turnpike], 1956 February 8 (Box 695)
  - Stamford Rotary Club, Stamford, Conn[ecticut], 1958 October 7 (Box 695)
  - Stamford-Greenwich Management Council, Annual Industry Night, 1960 January 14 (Box 695)
  - State Police Association of Conn[ecticut] Convention at Old Saybrook, Conn[ecticut], 1958 July 30 (Box 695)
  - [Station] WICC [Bridgeport] Statement by Gov[ernor] Ribicoff, [Absolute Maximum ]Speed Limit, 1960 April 29 (Box 695)
  - Station WICC – Kenneth Cooper [President] (Highway Safety) (Box 695)
  - Station WIP [Philadelphia], 1960 June 24 (Box 695)
  - [Station WMCA New York] Speech Taped by Gov[ernor] Ribicoff [Supporting Senator Kennedy as candidate for the Democratic Party nomination for President], 1960 March 11 (Box 695)
  - [Station] WNHC Recording [New Haven] (It Can’t Happen To Me), 1960 May 17 (Box 695)
  - Teachers, [Pay Raises for] [Storrs], 1956 October 26 (Box 695)
  - Television, Monday, 1958 November 3 (Box 695)
  - Television “Reorganization”, 1958 October 20 (Box 695)
  - Television, Monday, 1958 September 29 (Box 695)
  - Television, [Anniversary of Birth of] Theodore Roosevelt (Conservation), 1958 October 27 (Box 695)
  - Television, [Economic Growth of Connecticut], 1958 October 30 (Box 695)
  - Television, Industrial, 1958 October 13 (Box 695)
  - Temple Emanu–el, 50th Anniversary, Tucson, Arizona, 1960 February 28 (Box 695)
  - Thompsonville, Conn[ecticut], 1958 October 29 (Box 695)
  - Torrington Chamber of Commerce, 1958 January 29 (Box 695)
  - Torrington, Conn[ecticut], 1958 October 30 (Box 695)
  - Torrington Flood Project, 1959 August 29 (Box 695)
  - Traffic Safety, Governor’s Conference on, Yale University, 1960 April 2 (Box 695)
  - Traffic Safety Conference, Eastern Regional, Atlantic City, New Jersey; Also to New York Editors, 1956 May 1, December 12 (Box 695)
  - Traffic Safety Conference, 10th Annual Governor’s, California, 1959 October 8 (Box 695)
  - Vacation Advisory Council Meeting, Ocean Beach Park, New London, 1958 June 11 (Box 695)
  - Waterbury, Conn[ecticut], 1958 October 29 (Box 695)
  - Waterbury Chamber of Commerce, 1958 May 8 (Box 695)
  - Waterbury Sales Executive Club, Waterbury, Conn[ecticut], 1960 January 18 (Box 695)
  - Webster, Noah (Bicentennial) West Hartford, Conn[ecticut], 1958 October 16 (Box 695)
  - WNHC Dedication, 1959 September 11 (Box 695)
  - Willard, Emma, Speech [Commencement Address at Emma Willard School, Troy, New York, 1960 June 14 (Box 695)
  - Willimantic Chamber of Commerce, 1958 February 3 (Box 695)
  - Willow Garden Dedication for Elderly (Torrington), 1960 September 16 (Box 695)
  - Winsted Chamber of Commerce, 1956 April 18 (Box 695)
  - Woodmont Beach Erosion Project, 1959 August 19 (Box 695)
  - World Newspaper Forum, California Newspapermen’s [Association], Los Angeles, Cal[ifornia], 1960 October 13 (Box 695)
  - Yale University School of Medicine Sesquicentennial Celebration, New Haven, 1960 October 28 (Box 695)
- Series 8. Articles by or about Gov. Ribicoff
  This series is a type of clipping file of articles written by Gov. Ribicoff or about him. The files may include drafts and copies of final newspaper and magazine articles, interviews with TV or radio stations, transcripts of remarks and correspondence pertaining to the articles. These files overlap with main subject files, speech files, and press files.
  From AFL to World Telegram, the files are arranged alphabetically under the subset with a main heading, "Articles." Beginning with "John Bailey," the file arrangement is alphabetical with no subsets.
  - A[merican] F[ederation] of L[abor] State Convention [re: Ribicoff’s criticism of union activity at State mental hospitals], 1955 (Box 696)
  - Arden House Conference [on Metropolitan Area Problems, Harriman Campus of Columbia University, Harriman, New York], 1957 September 21-23 (Box 696)
  - American Chamber of Commerce Executives, Denver [Address by Governor], 1959 October 6 (Box 696)
  - Article – Bridgeport Herald, 1957 (Box 696)
  - Article – Ribicoff (by Herbert Brucker) [Editor, Hartford Courant, guest columnist for New London Day, “Ribicoff and Bailey Exercised Imagination in Backing Kennedy”], 1960 August 2 (Box 696)
  - Boston Herald, “Business Review and Forecast” [Article by Governor] (Box 696)
  - Christian Science Monitor, 1960 August (Box 696)
  - Christian Science Monitor, 1959 December (Box 696)
  - C[ongress] of I[ndustrial] O[rganizations] Yearbook [By Governor] [ Oct[ober] 1955 & State Labor Council Yearbook July 2, 1958] (Box 696)
  - Connecticut Circle [Photograph of Governor and Wife and inside note], 1955 January (Box 696)
  - Coronet [About the Governor’s first year], 1955 September (Box 696)
  - Conn[ecticut] Municipal Manual, Editorial [By the Governor], 1956 July 6 (Box 696)
  - Family Weekly, “Young Driver Problem” [Governor quoted in], 1960 May 29 (Box 696)
  - Harper’s Magazine [Article by Governor on Connecticut’s county government system], 1959 (Box 696)
  - Holiday Magazine [“How I Became a Connecticut Yankee,” by Jerome Weidman], 1959 September (Box 696)
  - Journal of American Insurance, [“Highways Can Be Happier Ways,” by Governor Ribicoff], 1960 June (Box 696)
  - Journal of Commerce, [Article about Governor and highway safety], 1960 March 3 (Box 696)
  - Keeping Posted [Article by Governor Not Sent] (Box 696)
  - Life Magazine [Article about election features Governor.], 1958 November 17 (Box 696)
  - Look Magazine, Highway Safety, [About the Connecticut program. Features Governor.], 1960 May (Box 696)
  - Look Magazine, New England Governor [“Abe Ribicoff: Connecticut Yankee”], 1960 September 13 (Box 696)
  - Mayor and Management [Guest Editorial by the Governor], 1960 March (Box 696)
  - Mechanix Illustrated [Article by the Governor re: highway safety], 1960 July (Box 696)
  - Milwaukee Journal, “County Government,” [Article by Governor], 1959 October 18 (Box 696)
  - Murphy, T.E., Hartford Courant [Article] about Governor Ribicoff, 1959 June (Box 696)
  - New Canaan Advertiser, Guest Column by Gov[ernor] Ribicoff for Carlton Hill [“A Citizen and His Public Role”], 1958 October 2 (Box 696)
  - New Haven Register, “The Connecticut Turnpike” (Box 696)
  - New York Age [Photograph at Ribicoff’s Inaugural Ball] (Box 696)
  - New York Herald Tribune, re: Anti-speeding Drive in Connecticut [Interview with Governor Ribicoff], 1956 June 25-26 (Box 696)
  - Newspaper [Articles About Governor, 1954-1957 (Box 696)
  - New York Mirror, Bill Slocum, “The Formidable Ribicoff”, 1959 September; 3 articles (Box 696)
  - New York Journal–American [Report of Tri – State Traffic Safety Commission], 1959 December 13 (Box 696)
  - New York [World] Telegram [and Sun], [Articles by] Allan Keller [on the Governor and holding the line on taxes], 1959 April 14-15 (Box 696)
  - New York Times (Highway Safety) [Article by the Governor), 1960 December (Box 696)
  - New York Times, (Industrial Expansion) [and Location] [Article by the Governor], 1956 (Box 696)
  - New York Times (flood planning) [Saturday Feature Magazine] [“Out of the Flood, A Better Future,” by Abe Ribicoff], 1955 October 9 (Box 696)
  - Newsweek [“Calling All Bureaucrats: How to Stay I the Black,” article about the Governor, p. 19], 1958 January 6 (Box 696)
  - Newsweek article [Article about the Governor], 1959 November 18 (Box 696)
  - Redlands Bulldog (University of Redlands, Redlands, California), [Articles about the Governor’s speaking engagement, October 1960] (Box 696)
  - Review, Connecticut [Request for statement from the Governor re: traffic safety and his response] (Box 696)
  - Saturday Evening Post, “Candid Congressman from Connecticut” [By T. E. Murphy], 1950 June 21 (Box 696)
  - Saturday Evening Post, “Slow Down in Connecticut”, 1956 (Box 696)
  - Sunday Herald [Bridgeport] [Article by Governor], 1960 (Box 696)
  - Think [Vol. 26, No. 6, p. 2 – 5] [“Get Tough and Be Safe!” by the Governor] planning in rebuilding after the flood, 1960 June (Box 696)
  - United Press International [Article by the Governor re: Accident Prevention Program] (Box 696)
  - USA, [Vol. VI, No. 9], “The Long and Lonely Road” [re: Governor Ribicoff’s fight with the legislature over taxes. He opposed their increase.] Winston–Salem, North Carolina, 1959 May 8 (Box 696)
  - World Telegram, (Allan Keller) [Two articles about the Governor’s budget fights], 1959 April (Box 696)
  - (Box 696)
  - The following folders pertain to subjects and individuals. (Box 696)
  - John Bailey (Box 696)
  - Bowles, Chester (Box 696)
  - Boys Club – Ribicoff (Box 696)
  - Louis B. Brandeis Memorial Lecture, David L. Bazelon (Box 696)
  - Businessmen in Politics (Box 696)
  - Prescott Bush (Box 696)
  - Candor in Politics (Article for James Cannon, Newsweek) (Box 696)
  - Degrees (Ribicoff) (Box 696)
  - Divorce Veto (Ribicoff), 1955 (Box 696)
  - Editorial Comments on Ribicoff (Box 696)
  - Editorial Comment (Ribicoff) (Box 696)
  - “Face the Nation”, 1960 (Box 696)
  - Feature Material on Ribicoff (Box 696)
  - Newsboy Experiences of Ribicoff, 1955 (Box 696)
  - Jon O. Newman (Box 696)
  - Remarks by Governor Ribicoff at WCCC Newspaperboys Program, 1959 May 25 (Box 696)
  - Newspaper Endorsements (Box 696)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Governor (Box 696)
  - Ribicoff for President (Box 696)
  - Governor Ribicoff – Political, 1960 (Box 696)
  - Ribicoff Family (Box 696)
  - Ribicoff – HEW Clippings, Articles, etc. (Box 696)
- Series 9. Press Files
  These files duplicate or overlap some of the Subject Files, Speech Files and Articles Files. Some files such as the Brotherhood speeches are not duplicated elsewhere. The contents are similar to those of the Articles Files.
  Arranged by subject.
  - Aging - Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 697)
  - American Dream (Ribicoff) (Box 697)
  - Amherst Commencement (Box 697)
  - Appointments (Box 697)
  - Appointments made by Gov. Ribicoff, 1959-1960 (Box 697)
  - Arden House Conference (Box 697)
  - Article - Business Week re: Connecticut's Current Budget, 1957-1959 (Box 697)
  - Articles - C.I.O. Yearbooks & State Labor Council (Box 697)
  - Article - Christian Science Monitor (Box 697)
  - [Article] Editorial - Conn[ecticut] Municipal Manualitorial - Conn[ecticut] Municipal Manual (Box 697)
  - Articles – Connecticut Review (Box 697)
  - [Article] Family Weekly Magazine “Young Driver Problem” (Box 697)
  - Article – County Government, Harper’s Magazine (Box 697)
  - [Article] Ribicoff – Journal of American Insurance (Box 697)
  - [Article] Journal of Commerce (Box 697)
  - Article – Keeping Posted (Box 697)
  - Article – Look Magazine, Highway Safety, 1960 May (Box 697)
  - Article – Mayor & Management (Box 697)
  - Article – Mechanix Illustrated (Box 697)
  - Article, County Government (Milwaukee Journal), 1959 October 18 (Box 697)
  - Article – New Canaan Advertiser (Guest Column by Gov[ernor] Ribicoff for Carlton Hill) (Box 697)
  - Article – New Haven Register, Connecticut Turnpike (Box 697)
  - Article – N[ew] Y[ork] Herald Tribune re: Anti-speeding Drive in Connecticut [Interview with the Governor], 1956 June (Box 697)
  - Article – New York Journal-American, 1959 December 13 (Box 697)
  - Article – New York Times, Highway Safety, 1960 November 9 (Box 697)
  - Article – New York Times (Industrial Expansion) (Box 697)
  - Article – New York Times (Flood Planning) (Box 697)
  - Article – Newsweek (Box 697)
  - Article – Saturday Evening Post, “Slow Down in Connecticut” (Box 697)
  - Article – The Sunday Herald, 1960 February 15 (Box 697)
  - Article – Think (Box 697)
  - Article – United Press International [magazine article] (Box 697)
  - Article – United Press Planning (Box 697)
  - Article – Western Union News (Box 697)
  - Baldwin, Chief Justice Raymond E. [re: ruling on speed laws] (Box 697)
  - Barnes, Senator Wallace [State Senator] (Box 697)
  - Barringer, Ben [State Senator] (Box 697)
  - Bazaars and Raffles [legislation] (Box 697)
  - Biographical [Governor Ribicoff] (Box 697)
  - Board of Pardons (Box 697)
  - Boat Laws (Box 697)
  - Briscoe, Robert – Lord Mayor of Dublin (Box 697)
  - Brotherhood [Henry G. Stetler, "Racial Integration in Private Residential Neighborhoods in Connecticut" (Hartford: Commission on Civil Rights)], 1957 (Box 697)
  - Brotherhood Speech Race Relations (Box 697)
  - Brotherhood Speeches by Governor Ribicoff [Jacoby Lectures, University of Bridgeport], 1957 February (Box 697)
  - Boston Herald Business Review and Forecast Bus Strike – Conn[ecticut] Co[mpany]), 1955 January (Box 697)
  - California Safety Patrol, Governor’s Safety Conference (Box 697)
  - California Trip, (re: Industry) [Economic Opportunities in Connecticut] [one large expandable folder], 1959 June 18-25 (Box 697)
  - Candor in Politics (Article for James Cannon, Newsweek) (Box 698)
  - Catholics (Box 698)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Political Workshop) (Box 698)
  - Chesebrough-Pond, Clinton (Box 698)
  - Children and Youth Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 698)
  - Christmas Message, 1955 – 1960 (Box 698)
  - Civil Defense, 3 folders (Box 698)
  - Civil Rights [Ribicoff’s opposition to Governor Faubus, 1957; Appointment of Attorney Boce Barlow as first black judge, 1957; Award given by New Haven Branch of NAACP, photographs, and Ribicoff’s speech with revisions], 1958 September 21 (Box 698)
  - Commencement Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 698)
  - Congregational Churches Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 698)
  - Connecticut Council of Churches – Statement by Gov[ernor] Ribicoff for Carl Clyma, 1957 January 7 (Box 698)
  - Connecticut Life (Box 698)
  - Connecticut Medical Service (Box 698)
  - Connecticut Turnpike Inspection Trip by Governor Ribicoff, 1957 October (Box 698)
  - Connecticut – Statistics – General (Box 698)
  - Connecticut, University of, [President] A. N. Jorgensen (Box 698)
  - Connecticut – Vacationland (Box 698)
  - Costello Visit to Connecticut [Prime Minister of Ireland], 1956 (Box 698)
  - County reform (Box 698)
  - Courts (Box 698)
  - Court Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 698)
  - Court Reform (Box 698)
  - Cranbury School Dedication (Box 698)
  - Cystic Fibrosis (Box 698)
  - Danbury (Box 698)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1956 (Box 698)
  - Democratic State Convention, 1956 (Box 698)
  - Development Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 698)
  - Devon, Liberty Rock Dedication, 1960 May 29 (Box 698)
  - Divorce Veto (Box 698)
  - Donnelly, Monsignor Joseph [Appointment of in 1959] (Box 698)
  - Economy Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 698)
  - Economy Order – Clippings [Governor’s ten percent reduction in state spending except for vital services and hiring freeze], 1957 November (Box 698)
  - Education Speeches by Governor Ribicoff, 2 folders (Box 698)
  - Eisenhower – Recession [March 1958 President’s request that states call special sessions of their legislatures in order to raise unemployment payments] (Box 698)
  - Eisenhower – Ribicoff (Box 698)
  - Emergency Powers (Box 698)
  - Enders, Ostrum (Box 698)
  - Face the Nation (Box 698)
  - Farm (Box 698)
  - Father’s Day (Box 698)
  - Fire Laws, Ribicoff (Box 698)
  - Fiscal Study Committee (Box 698)
  - Flaherty, Leo B. (Box 698)
  - Flood – Anniversary Report (Box 698)
  - Flood Comments (Box 699)
  - Flood Control Project Hearings in Washington by Public Works Committees of House and Senate (Box 699)
  - Flood – Industry (Southern) (Box 699)
  - Flood Statements by Ribicoff (Box 699)
  - Flood – Stories on Ribicoff (Box 699)
  - Flood – Washington Trip, February, 1956 (Box 699)
  - Ford, Norris W. (Box 699)
  - Forest Fire Hazard (Box 699)
  - Foster, Helen Case (Mrs.) re: her bid for State Senate (Box 699)
  - Furcolo (Box 699)
  - (Garroway Show) [Dave Garroway radio show, “Monitor”] [transcript of interview] (Box 699)
  - General Assembly Messages by Governor Ribicoff (Box 699)
  - Goodspeed Opera House [Foundation restoration] (Box 699)
  - Governors’ Conf[erence] Clippings, Atlantic City, 1956 (Box 699)
  - Governor’s Conference, Meteorological Research, 1958 May 21 (Box 699)
  - [Governors’ Conference Committee on] Federal – State Relations (Box 699)
  - Governors’ Conference, Miami Beach, Fl[orid]a, Clippings (Box 699)
  - Governors’ Conference – Miami Beach, Florida, 1958 May 18 (Box 699)
  - Hartford Probate District (Box 699)
  - Highway – “Connecticut Turnpike Dedication” (Box 699)
  - Highway Day Observance Luncheon – Wilmington, Del[aware], 1960 April 4 (Box 699)
  - Highways – Merritt Parkway (Box 699)
  - Highways – New London-Hartford Turnpike (Box 699)
  - Highway Dep[artmen]t Probe (Box 699)
  - Highway Reimbursement (Box 699)
  - Highways – Ribicoff (Box 699)
  - Highways Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 699)
  - Highway Safety Speeches by Governor Ribicoff (Box 699)
  - Highway Safety – Governors’ Conf[erence], Miami Beach, Florida, 1958 May (Box 699)
  - Highway – Statement of Frazar B. Wilde, President, Conn[ecticut] General Life Ins[urance] Co[mpany], 1959 April 8 (Box 699)
  - Highway Department, Stone and Webster Report on Study of (Box 699)
  - Highways – Turnpikes (Box 699)
  - Highways – Windsor-Windsor Locks Section of the Hartford-Springfield Expressway [I – 91], 1958 September 26 (Box 699)
  - Horan, Richard P. [Fund for slain FBI agent’s family] (Box 699)
  - Hurricane Notes, Donna, 1960 September 12 (Box 699)